### **ALMONZO RHODEN**

14 Lancaster CT, Apt H, Wayne, NJ, 07470

Phone: 862-438-2135 | Email: almonzo.rhoden@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/almonzorhoden/ Portfolio: https://almonzorhoden.github.io/

### SUMMARY

IT Professional with a background in Front End Development, Information Technology and customer service. Looking to work full-time in a corporate environment collaborating with others to utilize or develop acquired skills, knowledge, and more than 5+ years of experience in computer technology.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Application Analyst I St. Joseph Healthcare System

Paterson, New Jersey

September 2021 – Present

- Build/modify medical CPT/HCPCS codes and medication vaccines for doctors/staff to use in the system, so the organization can get maximum revenue for services.
- Participate in build, validation and QA testing procedures for implementation of software
- Communicate to project teams, clients and departments regarding system changes/updates

# Pc Tech St. Joseph Healthcare System

Paterson, New Jersey

November 2018 – November 2021

- Resolve complex problems in order to maintain computer system functionality
- Manage and update ticket queue with updates, so employees are aware of status
- Communicate incident to the appropriate IT teams to better escalate critical issues

# IT Technician Biotrial

July 2016 – August 2018

Newark, New Jersey

- Secure AD accounts (users and machines), password reset/unlocks, and user creation.
- Monitor ticketing queue, emails, and identify recurring problems and apply a resolution.
- Provide executive support, onboard train new hires, and current employees on new technologies.

### **SKILLSET**

**Languages:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive Design, Bootstrap, Github. **Other:** Microsoft Office, problem solver, Excel, project management, customer service, empathy, and a team player.

### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web Development Certificate March 2021: Rutgers University, NJ Bachelor of Arts, Information Systems May 2018: Rutgers University, Newark, NJ

References Available Upon Request